[singing "Nagisa" by Spitz]
I said this is pretty awesome!
[chuckles] Mm-hm.
[Taiki] Why do I feel
like we're getting closer?
[sighs contentedly]
The cultural festival is so fun!
Oh!
Huh?!
[Taiki grunts]
[growling]
[whimpering]
[continues growling]
[continues whimpering]
No!
[Taiki] I knew it,
there's no way I can do this.
[Niina] You're literally in costume.
What are you talking about?
Only 'cause you forced me to put it on!
You're the only one of us who can do it.
And the audience is waiting on you.
[Taiki] For a stand-in?
Hey, what about Kyo?
He knows all the lines.
[Niina] He got called to the committee.
[groans]
Please, Taiki.
You've watched over the whole production.
Can you please do this, so that
all of our work wasn't for nothing?
[Taiki] I have been here since day one,
and I know how hard they've worked.
[hopeful music playing]
[inaudible]
[Taiki sighs] Okay, fine. I'll do it.
I'll play Prince Charming.
[boy 1] That's what we wanted to hear!
[boy 2] That's real leadership!
We love you!
SNOW WHITE SCRIPT
- [Taiki sighs] Someone get me a script!
- [Niina] Here you go!
[Taiki] If I forget any of my lines,
you back me up!
Okay!
[opening theme song playing]
BLUE BOX
[all] Let's go! Taiki!
EPISODE 20
AS ONE OF HER CLOSEST FRIENDS
[Taiki] Sure. I've seen them
rehearse over and over.
I might not get every word perfect,
but I should know most of the lines.
So I'm gonna be fine.
[distorted noise]
Oh, who am I kidding?!
We're talking about me here,
the guy who's only been onstage to
play melodica in a grade school recital!
The guy who can't even say
"She sells she-shells by the..." [screams]
Is this the "unthinkable ordeal"
that Nishida was talking about?
I can just ad-lib the small stuff.
And if I mess up a line,
I can cover it up by singing.
Um... and then there's...
KISS
...this little problem.
[breath trembling]
I know, all I need to do is fake it.
But it will be impossible for me
not to think of the real thing.
Wanna do it for real?
[sighs]
I can't let it look awkward.
I'll get a seat right in the center.
[exclaims]
[groans]
And Chinatsu's going to be there.
Now it looks like I lied to her again.
It's not as if I can ask her not to come.
CHINATSU KANO
[music ends]
- [all applauding]
- [host] Thank you, everyone!
[Karen] Chii, over here!
You saved me a seat.
Uh-huh. Right at the very center,
just like you asked for.
Looks like they've got quite the crowd.
At my school, hardly anybody showed up
for the play performances.
Oh, look, it's Mr. Fortune Teller!
Yes, greetings.
[phone vibrating]
[Haryu] One guy in my class said
he was coming
just to see the rhythmic gymnastics girl.
[Karen] Oh, so she must be
pretty cute, huh?
Who's cuter, me or her?
Go on, young man, I don't mind.
You can tell me.
'Tis my lady Karen.
[Nishida] She's trained him well.
I guess normally you don't go to a play
unless there's someone you want to see
or you know somebody in the cast.
Is there anyone you know in the play?
I don't know anyone.
But I know some people behind the scenes--
- You know someone.
- [both] Mm?
Taiki Inomata.
He's playing Prince Charming.
Our Taiki?
Prince Charming?
All of a sudden,
I'm really looking forward to this.
Make sure you've got your camera ready.
[Nishida] Hm?
- How does Kano know he's in it?
- You two better be nice.
- Someone got injured, so he's standing in.
- It's love.
- Word's getting around fast.
- [Karen sighs]
TAIKI INOMATA
I'M GONNA BE IN THE PLAY! GO EASY ON ME!
YOU GOT THIS!
Hey, Imamoto.
Did you get the confetti ball set up
for the Best Class announcement?
Yeah, it's all set to go.
We barely managed
to finish it this morning,
so it was a bit of a rush job
to hang it up.
All right, good to hear.
Okay, the next performance up
is a play by the first-year students.
It seems that they've put their own
unique twist on a classic fairytale.
[softly] I know this was unexpected,
and I know anything can happen on stage.
But let's do this and enjoy it!
Let's go!
[all, softly] Yeah!
Let's go, Taiki!
Don't give up, Taiki.
You can do it.
[Taiki] I feel like I'm about to play
a badminton match.
I went through the script once at least.
As long as I don't freak out on stage,
I should be fine.
I couldn't help
but imagine the real thing.
Kissing you for real, Taiki.
Come on. Would you
stop thinking about that?
- A prince wouldn't stand like that!
- [grunts]
[grunts angrily]
[Hina] Are you feeling nervous yet?
Well, give it up 'cause this is happening.
What do you mean "give it up"?
Are you telling me you don't get nervous?
Who do you think this is
standing in front of you?
I'm the great Hina Chono.
[Taiki] Is that so?
[sighs]
[Hina] Yeah, of course, I'm nervous.
[exclaims softly]
It's way different from being in front
of people when I'm doing gymnastics.
And then there's the fact
I wasn't expecting you to be my partner.
[Taiki grunts softly]
[Hina] But you know,
I was cast in the lead role,
so it gave me a sense of responsibility,
and I've been rehearsing non-stop.
- [Taiki] Mm-hm.
- [Hina] So that's why...
I need you to really bring it.
Be there as one of my closest friends.
It's gonna be fine.
You'll never do anything more embarrassing
than that sports day.
[Taiki] Hey, that was
part of the act we planned!
Doesn't change the fact
it was terrible! [laughs]
We all had to participate!
Okay, then what about you in ninth grade?
I recall I was perfectly flawless!
Hey, guys, I'm back from the committee.
- [boy] No, man, I'm positive!
- Hm?
You think so?
What are you guys talking about?
[boy] Well, we were just wondering
if those two are going out! That's what.
They've always been pretty tight.
Uh, no, I'm pretty sure
they're just friends.
[boy] Seriously? I mean, look at them.
Yeah, you're not wrong.
I wonder what the difference is
between platonic friends...
and a relationship.
[buzzer sounds]
[host] We now present
Snow White by Year 1 Class B.
[classical music playing]
[narrator] Once upon a time,
the queen of the land gave birth
to a beautiful baby girl.
Her skin was as white as fresh snow,
and so, they called her Snow White.
[all exclaiming]
Snow White was cheerful and lively.
[Haryu] She is the rising star
of rhythmic gymnastics.
She shines up there.
[Karen] She looks
totally comfortable on stage.
You there!
Whatever are you doing
in a place like this?
[Haryu and Nishida snickering]
[Haryu] He's not making it a secret
that he's nervous.
[Karen] He's not even walking naturally.
But at least it's pretty obvious
he's giving it his all.
[Chinatsu gasps softly]
[Karen] Wait.
Was there always a scene in Snow White
where the prince shows up this early?
[Haryu] I hear their adaptation's
pretty different.
Apparently, someone said
it didn't make sense for the princess
to end up with a guy
who showed up out of nowhere.
So they added a scene at the beginning
where she meets the prince.
And that's when Snow White
falls in love with Prince Charming.
They changed it so that at the end,
the kiss is from someone she loves.
[gasps softly]
[girl 1] Our version
turned out great, huh?
[girl 2] I wouldn't wanna wake up being
kissed by someone I didn't know either.
It would be nice to end up
with the one you've always loved.
How romantic!
- [Ayame] Honestly?
- Huh?
If you ask me,
I'm not really into all that.
When you romanticize
long-time feelings for someone,
it really puts pressure on things.
Don't you think casual relationships
are way more fun?
Well, you're more uninhibited than us.
[Ayame] Yeah, cause the rest of you
are way too serious!
Come help us out for a while.
[witch student] Beautiful young lady,
I have a gift for you.
[Hina] Oh, my! What a beautiful apple!
Its skin is so red and glossy,
its bottom is so plump,
and its form so pleasing.
Indeed. I dare say
you're right, young miss!
[Hina] It looks to be the sweetest apple
I've encountered in quite some time!
We made it to the second half.
[Taiki] Oh goodness...
[boy] Taiki's really stressing himself out
over the kiss scene.
[Kyo] Well, it is the big moment.
So, Kyo, earlier,
- what we were talking about...
- She appears too lifelike to be dead.
[boy] You know, the difference between
platonic friends and a relationship.
[Kyo] Oh. Yeah, I remember.
My older brother told me
that the difference is...
whether...
[smooches] you'd kiss
the other person or not.
- [Taiki] Kiss?
- [coughs]
Maybe keep your voice down a little?
Oh, yeah, the audience might hear us.
That, too, but...
[boy] My brother's a free spirit.
It's one person's opinion.
But he says crossing the line
between friendship and relationship
is about the all-important kiss.
[Kyo] If that's the standard, then, Taiki...
[Taiki] Hm?
What are you guys talking about?
Keep your nose out of it.
[Taiki] Wait, you're shutting me out?
[shudders]
Right, right, right.
Now's the time to focus on the play!
[dwarves crying]
Goodness!
Whatever has become of you, my Snow White?
She appears far too lifelike to be dead.
Hina asked me to do this for her,
as one of her closest friends.
[Hina gasps]
Prince Charming!
[exclaims softly]
What's the big idea?
Are you trying to make a move on me?
What?
Another part they changed.
She's brazen.
[Taiki] Good. It's almost over.
Just the ending left now.
[exclaims softly]
[gasps]
Hina, watch out!
[all gasp]
[grunts softly]
[breath trembling]
- [boy] Are you okay?
- [Imamoto] Anyone hurt?
[all chattering]
[host] Uh, please accept our apologies.
We're gonna take a brief intermission.
Did they actually just kiss?
[boy 2] I think you're imagining it.
[girl 1] You should be worried
rather than gossiping.
[girl 2] They got hit
by the confetti ball.
I wonder if they're okay.
[girl 3] That was Chono and a guy
from badminton, I think.
[girl 4] They hang out together a lot.
They are dating, right?
[girl 4] Mm, I don't think so.
I told you,
it wasn't an actual kiss, okay?
With all the confetti,
I can see how it'd look like that.
I got close to her,
but we didn't touch at all.
Look are you just saying that, man?
Or are you just embarrassed?
Fess up, tell us the truth.
I told you already!
Well, Chono, is he telling the truth?
Yeah, he is.
[boy 1] Oh. Okay, yeah.
You must be aware, though. There's a rumor
making its way around the school
that the two of you are actually dating.
You are the prince and princess,
after all!
[boy 2] Even without the accident,
people would talk.
And really, you two had
great chemistry together on stage.
[boy 1] So the people who saw the play
are probably thinking the rumor's true.
I get it. I can see how
from your perspective
it might've looked like a real kiss.
But the way that
you all are joking about it
is not funny, so please stop.
I apologize.
[gloomy music playing]
[grunts]
[Taiki] I get the impulse to gossip. I do.
But who I'm dating
is none of their business.
[Hina] Taiki!
Sorry about all the rumors.
It's not like it's your fault, Hina.
If anything, I'm sorry.
I couldn't make the play a success.
That isn't true at all!
You remembered most of your lines.
And you were nervous in the beginning,
but got better and better.
You looked confident out there.
Your voice carried. And... and...
and then when you...
[exclaims]
You managed not to get overshadowed by me.
I commend you!
[Taiki] Well, then, as a thank-you,
how 'bout you do my homework?
- [Hina] It'll be full of mistakes.
- [Taiki] Never mind then.
- [chuckles]
- But, um, if you need me to...
I can explain the situation.
I can tell Chinatsu we didn't kiss,
just let me know!
Huh?
Well, you don't like
all of these rumors, right?
It seemed like it made you pretty mad.
And I want this all to be fair!
Oh, no, it wasn't...
I wasn't upset about that.
After-party in a bag.
You must be tired.
Thanks.
Geez, someone's hungry.
Gimme a break, just today!
Everyone's all, "Kiss this, kiss that."
Do they have nothing to say
about the play?
As a stand-in, I did pretty well, right?
[Kyo] Yeah, you did.
[grunts] But then, what was up
with that confetti ball?
What if someone had gotten hurt?
[Kyo] He's never in a bad mood.
[Taiki] And then there's Hina.
She thinks Chinatsu is the only reason
I'm mad about it.
Is it not?
[Taiki] Well, that's part of it, but...
more than anything, it's me and Hina
who are the ones being talked about.
With Hina, I don't know where I stand
in our relationship these days.
So I get caught up
on how to act sometimes.
I really hate people talking
about what we are.
And, honestly, I kinda figured Hina
is probably feeling the same way.
It seems like I'm the only one
who's mad, though.
I got a question, dude.
Yeah.
Are you not starting to have
feelings for Hina?
[soft music playing]
What?
With how many times
she's approached you about it,
it wouldn't be surprising if you are.
The person I like...
is Chinatsu.
Of course, it is.
I mean, I get the vibe that
you're like 100% into Chinatsu.
But I feel like you might've added
an extra 30% or so of feelings
for Hina, you know?
I think that's completely plausible.
That's all just...
hypothetical, though.
[groaning]
My head's killing me.
No matter how much it hurts,
really think it through.
[grunts]
[announcer on PA]
Everyone, thank you for your attendance.
That was a girl back there,
so I still have a chance.
[boy] Keep it movin'.
Do people from Kansai
eat takoyaki with rice?
It's that guy
who kissed the girl in the play.
- [announcer] Now, we officially bring...
- Really?
EIMEI FESTIVAL
...the 53rd Eimei Cultural Festival
to a close.
[Taiki] 100% coffee.
Thirty percent milk.
Tasty.
So it's possible to have a mixture
of feelings for both of them?
[exclaims]
Wait, no, that can't be!
[sighs]
Why does Kyo gotta say weird stuff?
The one I have a crush on is Chinatsu.
[groans, spits coffee]
[coughs]
Chinatsu, what are you doing here?
You're in my house?
My grandpa's doing well after his surgery.
So I'll be staying here again
starting tomorrow.
I came to bring some stuff.
[Taiki] I guess I knew
she was coming back soon.
Thanks again for taking me in, Taiki.
Uh, you're welcome.
Chinatsu saw what happened, too.
I wonder what she thinks about it.
[closing theme song playing]